宗教裁判所還是決定將西班牙交給圣殿騎士
The Inquisition has finally delivered Spain to the Templars.
蘇丹穆罕默德和他的軍隊仍堅守在格拉納達城內
Sultan Muhammad and his people still hold out in Granada.
但如果他兒子 那個王子 被抓了的話
But if his son, the prince, is captured,
他將開城投降 并獻上伊甸蘋果
he will surrender the city and the Apple of Eden.
你 阿圭拉 德 納爾哈
Do you, Aguilar de Nerha,
能宣誓信仰我們的信條 為自由而戰嗎
swear to honor our order in the fight for freedom?
為守護人類抵抗圣殿騎士的暴政
To defend mankind against Templars' tyranny,
守衛自由意志
and preserve free will?
我發誓
I swear.
如果蘋果落入他們手中
If the Apple falls into their hands,
圣殿騎士將摧毀擋在他們路上的一切
the Templars will destroy everything that stands in their way.
抗議 異議 還有為自己著想的權利
Protest, dissent, our right to think for ourselves.
向我宣誓你會不惜自己
Swear to me that you will sacrifice your life
和這里所有人的性命去守護它
and lives of everyone here to keep it from them.
遵命 導師
Yes, Mentor.
我們的生死無關緊要
Our lives are nothing.
蘋果才是重中之重
The Appleis everything.
雄鷹的靈魂 將守望未來
The spirit of the Eagle, will watch over the future.
當其他人盲目的追尋真相和真實的時候
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
記住 萬物皆虛
remember, nothing is true.
當其他人受到法律和道德的束縛的時候
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
記住 萬事皆允
remember, everything is permitted.
我們行走于黑暗 追尋于光明
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們是刺客
We are Assassins.
該死
Shit.
媽媽
Mom?
爸爸
Dad?
你的血不止屬于自己 卡爾
Your blood is not your own, Cal.
他們發現我們了
They've found us.
隱姓埋名 活在暗處
Live in the shadows.
快跑
Go! Go now!
你來這是為了拯救我的靈魂吧
You're here to save my soul.
差不多吧
Something like that.
我
I...
我知道今天是你生日
I understand it is your birthday.
是啊
Yeah.
派對這就要開始了
The party is just getting started.
坐下 你把我弄緊張了
Sit down. You're making me nervous.
主啊
Lord,
洗去我的罪惡
wash away my sin,
讓我再次
and I'll be clean...
變得干凈
Once again.
你不怎么相信圣經 是吧
You're not much for the Bible, are you?
特告知 卡勒姆 林奇
Be it known that Callum Lynch
被認定一級謀殺罪
has been found guilty of capital murder
被判今日執行死刑 2016年10月21日
and sentenced to die on this day, October 21st 2016.
犯人有臨終遺言嗎
Does the prisoner wish to make a final statement?
告訴我爸 我在地獄等他
Tell my father that I'll see him in hell.
我是索菲亞 里金博士
My name is Dr. Sophia Rikkin.
昨晚6點
At six pm yesterday evening,
你被處決并宣告死亡
you were executed and pronounced dead.
現在 所有認識你的人都認為
And so far, as anyone in the world knows or cares,
你已經離世
you no longer exist.
你最好還是坐下
It's better you to sit.
我的眼睛
My eyes...
你現在感覺到的不舒服是正常的
What are you feeling right now is normal and uncomfortable.
卡爾
Cal.
我是來幫你的
I'm here to help you.
而你也要幫我
And you're here to help me.
讓他走
Let him go.
別碰他
Don't touch him.
繼續呀 跳吧
Go ahead. Do it.
跳啊
Jump.
在這里你不再是個囚犯 卡爾
You're not a prisoner here, Cal.
我是來保護你的
I'm here to protect you.
如果你聽我的 一切才能行得通
If you listen to me, everything is going to make sense.
你需要相信我
And you need to trust me.
我在哪
Where am I?
你在馬德里的阿布斯泰戈基金會康復區內
You're in a rehabilitation wing of Abstergo Foundation in Madrid,
一個致力于完善人類的私人組織
a private organization dedicated to the perfection of human kind.
有了你的幫助 我們能夠開辟一條消除暴力的新道路
With your help, we can pioneer new ways to eradicate violence.
我能搞定
I had this.
你父親想讓他入伙
Your father wants him in.
他是我的病人
He's my patient.
這是我的項目
This is my program.
準備好阿尼姆斯
Prepare the Animus.
袖劍準備好了嗎
Are the blades prepared?
在這呢
Right here.
查到出處了沒
And we confirmed their provenance?
它們屬于阿圭拉
They belong to Aguilar.
我們在他的埋葬處找到的
We recovered them from his burial site.
這什么玩意
What are these?
執行最后準備 回溯到 1492年的安達盧西亞
Assume final preparations. Our regression, Andalusia, 1492.
全部都要記錄
Record everything.
機械手臂準備完畢
Arms ready.
這是干什么
What is this?
抱歉 卡爾 這不是我做事的風格
I'm sorry, Cal, this is not the way I like to do things.
那就別這么做
Then don't do it.
硬脊膜外麻醉注射
Insert epidural.
你到底想要什么
What do you want from me?
你的過去
Your past.
聽仔細了 卡爾
Listen to me carefully, Cal.
你即將進入阿尼姆斯
You're about to enter the Animus.
你所要看到的 聽到的 感受到的
What you are about to see, hear and feel,
都來自一個已經去世了五百年的人
are the memories of someone who has been dead for 500 years.
等一下
Wait a minute.
你無法改變過去 卡爾
You can't change what happens, Cal.
進行掃描
Engage scanner.
狀況怎樣
Status?
掃描DNA鏈 搜索時間范圍
Scanning DNA chains. Searching for time frame.
初始記憶已匹配鎖定
First memory match locked.
DNA配對完成
DNA match identified.
堅持住 卡爾
Stay with it, Cal.
嘗試同步
Attempt synchronization.
找到了 找到阿圭拉了
We found him. We found Aguilar.
同步成功
Synchronization achieved.
準備
There.
開始回溯
Commence regression.
我們的目標是那個男孩
Our mission is the boy.
是王子
It's the prince.
是誰庇護了他
Which household harbored the boy?
只有我
Only me.
沒有別人知道這件事了 沒了
Nobody else knew. Nobody.
把他的家人絞死 讓他看著
Hang his family and make him watch.
把村子燒光
Burn the whole village.
有格拉納達的王子作我們的俘虜
With the prince of Granada as captive, his father, Sultan,
他父親蘇丹就會帶著反抗的城市投降
will surrender his rebellious city,
交出最后一塊異教徒的避難所
the last safe haven for the infidels.
上帝會懲罰他們的異端邪說
God will punish his people's heresy.
只有圣殿騎士會最終統治西班牙
Finally Spain will be under one Templar rule.
呆在記憶里 卡爾
Stay with the memory, Cal.
阿圭拉 保護那個男孩
Aguilar! The boy, Aguilar! The boy!
阿圭拉 那個男孩
Aguilar, the boy!
拉出來
Pull him!
開始復原
Commence rehabilitation.
進行系統校驗 記錄他的情況
Run a system's check, and log his condition.
你做得很好 卡爾
You did well, Cal.
回看過去 世界歷史
Looking back it's clear that a history
顯然就是一部暴力史
of the world is history a violence.
去年反社會行為對經濟的影響
Last year the economic impact of antisocial behavior
達到了9萬億美元
was 9 trillion dollars.
我們認為 人們現今都壓抑著暴力行為
We believe that man today experiences
又難以找到合適的宣泄方式
a measure of aggression which he finds no acceptable outlets.
現在想象一下 如果這些損失都能被用到別的地方
Now imagine if all these costs could be channeled elsewhere...
回溯進行的好嗎
So the regression went well?
林奇是我們的實驗者
Lynch is the one.
作為阿圭拉的直系后裔
Direct descendent of Aguilar.
那里發生的一切都是那么的清晰 這還是第一次
Everything was clear in there, for the first time.
我們一直夢想什么 是一個更加和平安寧的世界
What do we all dream of? A more peaceful world.
我又盜用我的話
I see you stole my lines again.
誰讓你講的那么好
I only steal from the best.
伊甸碎片呢
And the artifact?
伊甸蘋果已經觸之可及了
The Apple. It's within our grasp.
里面究竟發生了什么 你為什么要拉他
What happened in there? Why did you pull him?
我必須這樣做 我們需要保證他的健康與安全
I had to. We have to keep him healthy.
讓他有自信 我相信他不會讓我們失望的
Earn his confidence. And I know he'll lead us to it.
推他下去
Push him.
阿尼姆斯不是這么用的
That's not how the Animus works.
好了
Here you go.
謝謝
Thank you.
1917年 盧瑟福分裂了原子
1917 Rutherford splits the atom.
1953年 沃森和克里克發現雙了螺旋結構
1953 Watson and Crick find a double helix.
2016年
2016 my daughter
我的女兒發現了治療暴力的方法
finds the cure for violence.
你總是比我做得更好
You've always been brighter than me.
我要遲到了
I'm late.
我要去向長老們匯報情況
I have to report to the Elders.
1492年 弗朗西斯科 里齊的作品 大審判
Francisco Rizi's Grand Inquisition. 1492.
戰爭 宗教迫害
War, religious prosecution,
神父托克馬達或是圣殿騎士中的一個人
and the closest that Father Torquemada or any of our Order
也在此時發現了伊甸蘋果
came to a finding the Apple of Eden.
你好嗎 我的朋友
How are you, my friend?
很好
Well.
閣下
Your Excellency.
下周長老院會面之時
Next week when the Elders meet,
我們應投票決定是否暫停阿布斯泰戈項目
we shall vote to discontinue your Abstergo project.
我們認為每年授予你的三十億美元
We feel that giving you 3 billion annually,
用在別處是個更好的選擇
could be better spent elsewhere.
三十億完全沒辦法和我的
Three billion is nothing compared to...
我們已經贏了
We've won.
人們已經不再關心他們的公民自由了
People are no longer care about their civil liberties,
他們關心的是生活水平
they care about their standard of life.
現代世界已經容不下自由這種概念了
The modern world has outgrown notions like freedom.
他們愿意跟隨我們
They are content to follow.
威脅仍會停留 自由也會存在
The threat remains while free will exists.
我們已經在宗教 政治和現在的消費主義上
For centuries we try with religion,
投入了幾個世紀的時間
with politics and now consumerism
就為了消除異教思想
to eliminate dissent.
難道我們現在不應該給科學讓路了嗎
Isn't it the time we gave a science a try?
我的女兒對此了解的比我們都要深刻
My daughter is closer than we've ever been.
你美麗漂亮的女兒還好嗎
How is your beautiful daughter?
她正在追蹤蘋果的守護者
She has traced protectors of the Apple.
在哪
Where?
后裔呢
The descendents?
幾乎所有的后人都死了
All the blood lines have died out.
但還剩一個
But one.
我們在五百年前找到了他 在刺客兄弟會
We've traced his back 500 years, to the Assassin's Brotherhood.
通常錯覺就是我們通常說的出血效應
Hallucinations are what we call the "Bleeding effect."
試想你的回溯
Images of your regression,
可以感受到你現在的視角
laying themselves over your present day field of vision.
如果你允許的話 我可以教你怎樣控制他們
If you allow me, I can teach you how to control them.
退后 我能解決的
Stand down. I have this.
聽她的
Let it be.
那是什么 那個機器
What is it? The machine?
這是基因記憶
It's genetic memory.
通過阿尼姆斯
By using the Animus,
可以重現我們祖先的生活
we can relive lives of those who made us who we are.
我在那里看到的 感覺很真實
What I saw in there, it felt real.
就是真的
It was.
某種程度來說
In a way.
別跟我扯淡
Don't mess with me!
我現在感覺自己不一樣了
I feel different now.
為什么這么激動
Why the aggression?
我性格就這樣
I'm an aggressive person.
這個監獄是干什么的
What kind of prison is this?
這里不是監獄 卡爾
It's not a prison, Cal.
你配合
You'll learn more if you cooperate.
放開我
Let me go.
我餓了
I'm hungry.
跟我來
Come with me.
這是什么
What is this?
我對你了如指掌 卡爾
I know everything about you, Cal.
你的醫療記錄 心理檔案
Your medical data, your psychological profile,
以及你的MAO-A基因突變
the mutations in your MAO-A gene.
我知道你寄養家庭的事情
I know about the foster homes.
還有你在少管所的事情
The juvenile homes.
你就是遺傳型犯罪活生生的例子
You are a living proof of the link between heredity and crime.
你怎么找到的我
How did you find me?
我們發現了阿圭拉
We found Aguilar.
當你被捕的時候 你的DNA和他的匹配
When you were arrested, your DNA matched his.
- 阿圭拉是誰 - 你的祖先
- Who is Aguilar? - Your ancestor.
他的家族曾經是刺客
His family were Assassins.
他們被圣殿騎士 托爾克馬達
They were burnt at the stake by the Templars,
和你看到的暗黑騎士奧赫達燒死在了火刑柱上
Torquemada and the black knight you saw, Ojeda.
阿圭拉接過了刺客教團的使命
Aguilar took up the Assassins' cause.
你經常出去嗎
Do you go out much?
比你多
More than you.
那這里的其他人呢 也都是小白鼠嗎
And the others in here? Are they the lab rats too?
他們是刺客 像他們祖先一樣的殺人犯
They are Assassins, murderers like their ancestors.
像你一樣 卡爾
Like you, Cal.
生來就帶有暴力傾向
All born with predisposition to violence.
殺人犯
Murderer?
- 你殺了那個人 - 一個皮條客
- You killed the man. - A pimp.
你還會再殺人嗎
Would you kill again?
幸福的家庭
Happy families.
她一定很為你自豪
She must be very proud.
我無法得知她的想法了
I wouldn't know.
她被一個刺客所殺
She was killed by an Assassin.
就像你母親一樣
Like your mother.
抱歉
Sorry.
我老爸殺了我媽媽
My old man killed my mother.
你對此是什么感覺
And how does that make you feel?
我想殺了他
Like killing him.
我們要么讓它影響我們一生
Either we let it to effect us for the rest of our lives,
要么會為之改變
or we just do something about it.
你變得暴力 我投身科學
You turn to violence, I turn to science.
這是伊甸蘋果 卡爾
It's the Apple of Eden, Cal.
我相信它真實存在
I believe it exists.
圣經告訴我們
The Bible tells us it
它包含了人類第一次反叛的根源
contained the seed of man's first disobedience.
而我們相信
But there are those of us who believe that
神或者其它遠古文明
God or some ancient civilization
給我們留下了理解人類為何會有暴力的指路圖
have left us a road map to understand why people are violent.
阿圭拉是所知的最后一個
Aguilar was the last
擁有這個蘋果的人
person known to have had it in his possession.
我們需要你來找出他把它藏在了哪里
We need you to find out where he hid it.
我還以為我來這里是接受治療的
I thought I was here to be cured.
暴力是一種病
Violence is a disease.
像癌癥一樣
Like cancer.
就像癌癥那樣 有朝一日我們希望能夠控制它
And like cancer, we hope to control it one day.
暴力支撐著我活到現在
Violence is what kept me alive.
嚴格意義上來說 你已經死了
Well technically, you're dead.
我餓了
I'm hungry.
我能得到什么好處
What's in it for me?
一旦我的研究完成
Once my research is complete,
你就沒必要待在這里了
there is no reason to keep you here.
我能拿回我的人生嗎
I get my life back?
比這更好 全新的生活
Better. A new one.
你餓了
You are hungry.
你不了解他是誰 他是怎么樣一個人
You don't know who he is, what he is.
他是個危險的男人
He is a dangerous man.
再給他點時間 埃米爾
Give him little more time, Emir.
要給人機會去證明他還留存這高貴的血液
Man may prove that has some noble blood in him yet.
坐這里怎么樣 先生
How about here, sir?
想點什么都可以 不過我們推薦雞肉
It's an open menu, but we do recommend a chicken.
您想吃點什么嗎 林奇先生 點什么都可以
What can I get you, Mr. Lynch? It's an open menu,
但我們推薦雞肉
but we do recommend a chicken.
我要牛排
I'll have steak.
給先驅者上牛排
Steak for the pioneer.
你是誰
Who are you?
大家叫我穆薩
They call me Moussa.
但我的名字是巴蒂斯特 我已經死了200年了
But my name is Baptiste. I'm dead 200 years now.
巫毒師
Voodoo poisoner.
我是人畜無害的
I'm harmless.
他們在觀察你
Ah  They're watching you.
等著看看你到底是誰 先驅者
Waiting to see who you are, pioneer.
你見過他了嗎
Have you met him yet?
我們是蘋果的最后保護者 朋友
We are the last to protect the Apple, my friend.
選錯了 你將讓我們全都萬劫不復
Pick the wrong choice, you'll send us all to infinity.
這個
This...
是屬于你的
belongs to you.
你會直接帶領他們找到伊甸蘋果嗎
You're going to lead them right to it.
不 我要吃了它
Ne, I'm going to eat it.
到底怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
他必須再次進入阿尼姆斯
He has to go back in the Animus.
就現在
Now.
再次進去前他還需要更多時間
He needs more time before he goes in again.
我們沒時間了
We don't have time.
為什么
Why?
我不會拿他的命冒險
I won't risk his life.
那我只能吩咐別人去做了
Then I'll have to find someone else to do it.
- 你睡醒啦 重拳手 - 我瘋了
- You're up, slugger. - I'm crazy.
我瘋了
I'm crazy.
孤獨使我瘋狂
Crazy for feeling so lonely.
他們把他又抓回去了
They're getting him back in again.
我們要在他背叛我們之前采取行動
We should stop him before he betrays us.
把日期調到6號
Set the date for the six.
如果他的情況出現惡化 那就停止實驗
If his condition deteriorates, pull him out.
- 可是你的父親 - 我不在乎他說了什么
- You father... - I don't care what my father said.
#何負於天下#
What in the world did I do?
- 卡爾聽我說 - #強至不能 戰至感己#
- Cal, listen to me. - I'm crazy for trying...
聽我說 你一定要跟阿圭拉保持同步
Listen to me. You have to stay with Aguilar.
#淚決堤#
Crazy for crying...
如果你停留在同步真空里 將會非常危險
Staying in synch-void could be dangerous.
#且為你癡狂#
And I'm crazy for loving you...
很快他們就會向格蘭納達進發
Soon they will march on Granada.
穆罕默德蘇丹的實力很弱
Sultan Muhammad is weak.
他不僅會交出伊甸蘋果
He'll surrender the Apple
還會為了救王子而背叛信條
and betray the Creed to save the prince.
情欲使吾儕軟弱
The love makes us weak.
幸然已鞠躬盡瘁
Gladly I'll sacrifice my flesh and blood,
只為信條永存
for survival of the Creed.
如果我死了 不要為我哭泣
When I die today, don't waste your tears for me.
耶和華訓示我們
The Lord spoke.
主說
And he said:
那不常跟我連結的人要被扔掉
"If a man abide not in me
像枯干的枝子 讓人撿去投在火里焚燒
he is cast into the fire
他將被焚燒
and he is burned!"
數十年來
For decades,
因為異教徒 我們活在支離破碎的
you have lived in the world torn apart
悲慘世界里
by religious discord.
但現在 多虧了主的榮恩
But soon, thanks to God
和宗教審判
and Inquisition
我們終將清除惡疾
we will purge this disease!
現在站在你們面前的罪人
The sinners before you,
曾試圖保護格拉納達的異教徒王子
sought to defend the heretic prince of Granada,
格拉納達是我們圣戰中
the last heathen stronghold
最后一個異教徒據點
in our holy war.
今天
So today,
在我們國王和王后的見證下
before our king and queen
我發誓我們將要在主賜的圣火中
I swear we shall wash ourselves clean,
洗濯污穢
in the holy fire of God!
親眼目睹
Behold...
主的旨意
God's will!
你們要看著你們的導師先被燒死
You will watch your mentor
然后你們再慢慢被折磨至死
burn and then you will die the slowest.
為了明日榮耀
Give glory to the future.
愿犧牲自己
Not to us.
他同步了
He is synchronizing.
可惡的異教徒
Damned heretics!
別讓他們跑了
Don't let them escape!
快跳
Jump.
斷開同步完成
Complete desynch.
把他放下來
Get him down!
叫醫護人員過來
Call the medics!
沒事的 別出事 卡爾
Okay. It's okay. Cal, stay with me. Cal.
別 沒事的 快點啊
Stay... It's okay. Hurry up!
好了 看看我
Okay. Okay. Look at me.
看著我
Look at me.
我的腳沒有知覺了
I can't feel my legs.
暫時的麻痹而已
Paralysis is temporal.
那壞消息是什么
What's the bad news?
它導致你的系統神經斷裂 但這次我們會幫你
It caused a neurological split but we got you through it.
渡過難關
This time.
我遲早會死在這兒的 對吧
I'm gonna die in here, aren't I?
不會
No.
如果你能主動進去同步 你就不會死
Not if you go in there on your own free will.
我做不到
I can't do this.
不 你能做到的
Yes, you can.
伊甸蘋果 你是唯一一個能找到它的人
The Apple. You're the only one left who can find it.
我們可以了結這一切痛苦 卡爾
We can put an end to pain, Cal.
為了全人類
For everyone.
你從哪里找到的
Where did you get this?
我父親在你母親死的時候找到的
My father recovered it from the scene of your mother's murder.
然后把它帶到這里妥善保管
And brought it here for safekeeping.
妥善保管
Safekeeping?
明明就是你把它偷走了
You stole it.
這是你母親的項鏈 我希望能物歸原主
It's your mother's necklace. I wanted you to have it.
他當時為什么會在那里
Why was he there?
- 為了救她 - 誰要殺她
- To save her. - From whom?
- 她自己人 - 那和你們有什么關系
- Her own people. - What's that got to do with you?
刺客與圣殿騎士之間的爭斗已經持續了數世紀
Assassins and Templars have been at war for centuries.
我的目標是改變這個局面
I aim to change that.
說的真好聽 我差點都忘了
That's right, I forgot.
我們的目的是戰勝暴力
We're here to combat aggression.
我想我可能不太吃你這一套
I don't think I like your methods.
我是個科學家
I am a scientist.
我在這兒是為了治愈暴力傾向
I'm here to be cured of violence.
那又有誰會來治愈你
Who's gonna cure you?
我們這是養虎為患
We're feeding the beast.
我們讓他越來越強大了
We're making him stronger.
我是里金醫生
I am Dr Rikkin.
叫我艾倫就好
Alan.
我在這兒管理阿布斯泰戈工業公司
I look after things here in Abstergo.
家族式企業 是嗎
You like to keep the things in the family, huh?
是的
Yes.
如果我們讓你覺得不適 我先道個歉
I'm sorry if we caused you any discomfort.
我有什么能夠幫得上忙嗎
Is there anything I can do?
那就放我出去吧
How about you let me out of here?
這個請求超出我的管理范圍
That's something I can't manage.
我是來跟你做個交易的
I'm here to make a deal.
我們需要伊甸蘋果
We need the Apple.
并且需要你幫我們拿到
And we need you to get it for us.
你在阿尼姆斯中已斷開同步連接
You've been desynching in the Animus.
我們需要你恢復同步
We need you not to do that.
要把我送回機器里嗎
Sending me back to the machine?
不必 你展現給我們的已經足夠了
No, you've already shown us what we needed to see.
那你會放我們自由嗎
Will you let us free then?
你究竟想從新來的那里獲取什么
What do you hope to gain from the newcomer?
對我們所有人都有好處的東西
Something that'll benefit us all.
你呢 穆薩
You too, Moussa.
你對他們做了什么
What have you done to them?
這就是依靠自己的意志力
It's what happens if you
進入回溯失敗的結果
don't enter in regression on your own volition.
還認得它嗎
Do you recognize this?
這是袖劍
It's Assassin's blade.
這就是當時
This is the actual one...
你父親奪取你母親性命的兇器
your father used to take your mother's life.
他在這里 你知道嗎
He's here, you know?
母親的死亡
Mother's death, Cal.
這不是一個孩子應當面對的場景
Not something a boy should ever be made to see.
你不該那樣
This is wrong.
我別無他選
You left me no choice.
你說過 他必須靠自己的意志進入
He has to go in on his own free will, you said that.
- 我必須進行交涉 - 你是說操縱吧
- I had to negotiate. - You mean manipulate?
我向長老院保證我們會把伊甸蘋果帶到倫敦
I assured the Elders we would have the Apple for London.
只剩兩天時間了
That's in two days.
他不愿了解自己的過去或者親生父親
He doesn't want to know his past, or his father.
他只想將兩者并皆摧毀
He wants to destroy them, both.
我們可不是要干創造怪物的勾當
We're not in the business of creating monsters.
我們既不創造他們也不毀滅他們
We neither created them nor destroyed them.
我們只是放任他們于不可抵抗的信仰之中
We merely abandoned them to their own inexorable faith.
- 你是你母親所生 - 這說明什么
- You're your mother's son. - What does that mean?
你身體里流淌的血液并非只屬于你自己
Blood that flows through you is not your own.
它屬于信條
Belongs to the Creed.
你母親早就知曉
Your mother knew that.
因她的死亡 信條才得以存活
She died so the Creed may live.
講清楚
Remind me how, exactly!
如你所見 是我所為
What you saw, I did.
你殺了她
You murdered her.
我寧可親自動手也不愿她被那個機器奪去生命
I took her life rather than have it stolen by that machine.
男人經歷考驗才能成長
Man grows with the greatness of his task.
我本該殺了你
I ought to have killed you.
但下不了手
I couldn't.
那就現在
Well, here.
殺了我
Take it.
完成你30年前該做的事
Do what you couldn't do 30 years ago.
袖劍現在在你的手里了 卡爾
It's in your hands now, Cal.
這是他們想要見到的
This is what they want.
讓我血濺當場
Spill my blood.
但是別回阿尼姆斯
But do not go back in the Animus.
為什么
Why?
伊甸蘋果蘊藏著自由意志的基因密碼
The Apple contains the genetic code for free will.
他們將利用這點消滅我們
They will use it to destroy us.
我會找到伊甸蘋果
I'm gonna find it.
親眼見證他們毀滅你和你的信條
And watch them destroy you and your Creed.
你不可能消滅信條
You can not kill the Creed.
信條已融于你的血液之中
It's in your blood.
伊甸蘋果就是一切
The Apple is everything.
你母親為了保護它而死
Your mother died to protect it.
她別無選擇
She had no choice.
我有
I do.
你要去毀滅信條
You're gonna kill the Creed!
帶我去阿尼姆斯
Take me to the Animus.
讓我進入
Put me in.
機器準備
Prepare the Animus.
自愿回溯
Voluntary regression.
你知道刺客名字的由來嗎
Do you know how the Assassins came to be named?
它來源于阿拉伯文字 Hashashin
From an Arabic word "Hashashin".
他們屬于社會的異類
They were society's outcasts.
偷盜之人 死于非命之人
Those who stole, who murdered in cold blood.
遭唾棄之人 反叛者 愚蠢者 癮君子
People ridiculed them... Rebels, fools, drug addicts.
但他們又是睿智之人
But they were wise.
他們利用這點來掩藏
They used this reputation to hide the dedication to principles
超越他們最強勁敵的信仰法則
beyond those of even their strongest enemies.
為此我敬重他們
And for that I admire them.
但你不是他們其中一員
But you're not one of those men.
是嗎
Are you?
我們走著看
Let's find out.
啟動回溯
Commencing regression.
這是我的畢生之作
This is my life's work.
這是我的人生
It's my life.
為了信條
For the Creed.
我們自己的人生
Our own lives...
重要的是我們曾留下的
What matters is what we leave behind.
蘇丹
Sultan...
交出伊甸蘋果
Surrender the Apple.
你的刺客護衛已死
Your Assassin protectors are gone.
信條已亡
The Creed is finished.
我的孩子
My son.
人類首次反抗和
Here lies the seed
自由意志的根源
of man's first disobedience,
就在于此
of free will itself.
多虧伊甸蘋果
Thanks to the Apple of Eden,
這已知世界
the known world
將迎來新紀元
shall be ushered into a new age.
新和平
One of peace,
那里所有征戰的人類
in which all the warring populations of mankind
都將絕對服從于
shall bow in perfect obedience
圣殿騎士的統治
to our one templar rule.
伊甸蘋果
The Apple.
交給他
Give it to him.
立刻
Now.
為了信條
For the Creed.
快
Go!
原諒我
Forgive me.
都結束了
It's over!
刺客
Assassin!
信仰之躍
A leap of faith.
這是在哪兒
Where are we?
這里看起來像軍事港口
It looks like a military port.
維爾瓦省 防空識別區
Kadiz, Palos de la Frontera.
刺客們為它犧牲性命
The Assassins died for it.
你要用生命守護好它
Protect it with your life.
我是刺客集團的友軍
I am a friend of the Creed.
把它帶進你墳墓里
Take it to your grave.
我發誓
I swear.
他說了什么 翻譯出來
What is it? Translation.
追隨太陽之光芒
Following the light of the sun,
我將棄舊世于身后
I shall leave this old world behind.
他是克里斯托弗 哥倫布
It's Christopher Columbus.
他埋在哪了
Where is he buried?
他的遺體被遷回西班牙
His remains were returned to Spain.
墳墓在塞維利亞大教堂
His tomb is in Seville Cathedral.
我們找到了
We found it.
帥哥們 過來下
Hey All Stars, come here.
選一個
Pick one.
隨便哪個
Anyone.
- 公共休息室遭攻破 - 封鎖阿尼姆斯
- Breach in common room. - Seal the Animus.
這是記憶嗎
Is it a memory?
不是
No.
來吧
Come on!
- 直升機呢 - 待命中
- Transport? - Standing by.
保護阿尼姆斯 處理掉其他人
Protect the Animus. Purge the facility.
我得先把你護送出去
I need to get you out of here first.
- 不行 - 我們必須得走 索菲亞
- No! - We have to leave, Sophia.
不
No!
不要
繼續戰斗
Pick it up!
你不是孤單一人 卡爾
You are not alone, Cal.
從來不是
You never were.
- 開門 - 快點
- Open... - Come on.
當其他人盲目的追尋真相和真實的時候
Where other men blindly follow the truth,
- 記住 - 萬物皆虛
- remember... - Nothing is true.
當其他人受到法律和道德的束縛的時候
Where other men are limited by morality or law,
- 記住 - 萬事皆允
- remember... - Everything is permitted.
我們穿行于黑暗 追尋于光明
We work in the darkness to serve the light.
我們是刺客
We are Assassins.
現在怎么做 先驅者
What now, pioneer?
戰斗
We fight.
閣下
Your Excellency.
榮耀屬于你父親
The glory will go to your father.
但我們都清楚是誰找到了伊甸蘋果
But we both know who found it.
你的時代即將來臨 我的孩子
Your time will come, my child.
他們會給你的成就頒諾貝爾和平獎
They'll give you a Nobel peace prize for this.
你最好開始寫獲獎致辭了
You better start writing your speech.
- 我讀了你的演講稿 - 怎么
- I've read yours. - And?
如果根除自由意志 我們就能鏟除刺客
If we eradicate free will, we eradicate the Assassins.
這些瘡害社會數百年的毒瘤
A cancer that has menaced society for centuries.
這篇不是我最出色的稿子 但扼住了要點
It's not my best work, but it gets the point across.
我們一直在尋找出路
We've been looking for solutions.
你解決了這個問題
You've eliminated the problem.
所以說 我的項目
So my program...
第一次為社會帶來了秩序
Has brought order to society for the first time.
我對這件事負責
I'm accountable for this.
早有人為你的行為負責
You've already been accounted for.
我們做的一切都屬于長老院
Our work belongs to the Elders.
現在是他們的決勝時刻
This is their finest hour.
你騙了我
You lied to me.
我一直都知道
I've always known
在你心底 科學第一 圣殿騎士第二
that in your heart you're a scientist first, templar second.
你近期的成就令人震撼
Your recent work has impressed as much
但也證實了我們的信條
but it has confirmed our belief that mankind
人類無法被救贖
cannot be redeemed.
你一切都算計清楚了
You've thought of everything.
也不盡然
Not quite. My speech.
我的演講需要你簡練大方的開場白
It could do with one of your elegant openings.
如今我成了死神
Now I've become death,
世界的毀滅者
the destroyer of worlds.
這話似乎上不了臺面
Not sure that I could make that work.
今晚我無比榮幸在此介紹
It is with great pleasure tonight that I introduce
我們遵從古訓之未來的締造者
the architect of our ancient order's future.
讓我們歡迎阿布斯泰戈公司的首席執行官
Please welcome the CEO of Abstergo Foundation,
艾倫 里金博士
Dr. Alan Rikkin.
重獲伊甸蘋果之后
With the recovery of the Apple,
我們現已掌握
we are now in possession
決定人類天性與本能的
of the complete genetic road map
完整基因譜圖
to humanity's instincts.
任何對于獨立
Any impulse towards independence,
抵抗和反叛的沖動
resistance or rebellion
都將被瓦解
will be crushed.
任何可能阻礙我們時代前進步伐的傾向
Any predisposition that might oppose our march of progress
現可被根除
can now be eradicated.
我只想大呼
All I have to do is shout.
我是來幫你的
I'm here to help you.
而你也要幫我
And you're here to help me.
我無法再幫你了
I can't help you anymore.
那些宏偉的計劃呢
What about all those great plans?
治療暴力 戰勝侵略性
Cure violence, combat aggression.
這些都不可能發生了
That's not going to happen.
此事因你而起 蘇菲亞 別想一走了之
You've started this, Sophie. You don't get to walk away.
我們都知道接下來會變成怎樣
We both know what happens next.
不是所有人都有資格活在世上
Not everything deserves to live.
我不能這么做
I can't do this.
你可以的
Yes, you can.
但這不是為了我們自己
But it is not to ourselves,
而是我們必須給予榮耀于未來
but to the future, that we must give glory.
迎接一個徹底清除刺客集團的未來
A future purged of the Assassin's Creed!
女士們 先生們
Ladies and gentlemen,
伊甸蘋果
the Apple of Eden.
這是我造成的
I did this.
我會為長者會奪回伊甸蘋果
I will retrieve the artifact for the Elders.
我要為自己拿回來
Lynch I want for me.
這不是為了我們自己
It is not to ourselves,
而是為了未來 我們必須給予榮耀
but to the future, that we must give glory.
本字幕由Orange字幕組傾情制作，歡迎大家加入Orange字幕組，字幕組長期招收翻譯，校對，時間軸，壓制等職位，有意愿者請加群：489216448 歡迎大家加入粉絲群：259110198
鄭重聲明:本作品之片源、字幕均來自互聯網，版權歸原電影公司所有。任何組織和個人不得公開傳播或用于任何商業盈利用途，否則一切后果由該組織或個人承擔！本站和制作者不承擔任何法律及連帶責任！請自覺于下載后24小時內刪除。如果喜歡本片，請購買正版！
翻譯  pelf 卜卜 CC 夏目 Alison UE
校對  P.E. 圣殿騎士球球
特效 壓制  解藥上神
m 10.375 -172.875 b 3.375 -220.375 33.375 -275 172.875 -257.875 b 147.125 -237.5 136.625 -212.5 113.75 -192.25 b 89.625 -182.875 56.25 -170.375 13.75 -172.875 m -110.375 140 b -360.375 -4.75 -110.375 -267.25 147.125 -127.5 b 147.125 -127.5 103.375 -90 103.375 -90 b -97.125 -185.375 -239.625 15 -70 97.875 b -70 97.875 -110.375 140 -110.375 140 m -70 97.875 b 83.375 160.375 239.625 10.375 103.375 -90 b 103.375 -90 147.125 -127.5 147.125 -127.5 b 339.625 15 116.625 235.375 -110.375 140 b -110.375 140 -70 97.875 -70 97.875
Orange字幕組
歡迎關注我們的微博
幾個世紀來 圣殿騎士團一直在
尋找著神秘的伊甸蘋果
他們堅信里面不僅包含人類第一次反抗的根源
還有自由意志的關鍵
如果他們找到遺物并解開其中的秘密
他們就擁有了控制所有自由意志的能力
只有刺客兄弟會在阻止他們
安達盧西亞 西班牙
1942年
刺客信條
加利福尼亞半島
墨西哥 1986
30年后
亨茨維爾監獄
德克薩斯州 美國
1492年的安達盧西亞
Andalucia, 1492.
阿基拉爾 狄 尼赫拉
1455-1526
大圣殿禮堂
倫敦
卡勒姆 林奇引起的恐慌在滋長
你認識這名少年嗎？
黑幫
林奇將死
法官宣判皮條客
殺手有罪
侵入
當地
林奇
1979-現今
警局